Very well, Lord Ains,
I will take my leave now.
Outstanding work. Keep the first floor
of Nazarick safe until we return.
As you wish.
Gate.
I apologize for the place
being so run-down, Lord Ains.
I was in a rush to get it ready
when I heard that you would be coming.
There is no need to be concerned.
You built this place for me,
so it is on par with even Nazarick.
Right!
Still, Aura, tell me one thing--
what is that?
Plain though it may be,
we prepared a throne for you.
What kind of bones are those?
Various different animals.
We assembled the best parts
of griffons, wyverns, and the like.
That's not what...
I see.
I don't care how you look at it,
those appear to be human bones, too!
I'm supposed to sit on that?
Shalltear...
I promised you I would give you
your punishment, right?
This is the perfect time.
I will give it to you now.
Yes, your humiliation.
Indeed! Brilliant!
Sorry, Demiurge. This is the way it is.
Seating yourself on a guardian?
Truly, such is a seat
worthy of the Supreme One,
which is to say,
one which no other could claim!
Leave it to you, Lord Ains.
I never even thought of this!
O-Oh, no?
Lord Ains, may I be excused
from the room for a moment?
I will return at once.
Hmm, well, all right. Go on.
Thank you very much.
I am back, Lord Ains.
Uh, mm-hmm.
Ah yes, Aura, when I left the room,
I bumped into the wall by mistake.
It appears to have been damaged.
Could you fix it up later for me?
I'm sorry about that.
Okay.
Shalltear, is this too hard on you?
--If so--
--It is not hard on me at all!
On the contrary, I take it as a reward!
No, this is the punishment
I gave to Shalltear.
Besides, Shalltear's slip-up
came about due to my failure.
Which means that suffering
through my desire to get out of this
is my punishment to myself.
Still, Peroroncino, just how kinky
did you configure her to be?!
All right, down to business.
Do you think we did
a decent job of alarming them?
I think it was perfect, Lord Ains.
Absolutely. Did you see
those Lizard Men's faces?
I see. Then I suppose the first stage
of the demonstration that Cocytus
hoped for was successful enough.
Now...
...how about a look at
what the Lizard Men are up to?
They're wasting their efforts.
Those would be the chiefs.
Hmm? The white one and the one
with the magic weapon aren't there.
Zaryusu was his name, wasn't it?
Ah, yes. That was his name.
Maybe he's inside one of the houses.
He could be.
Normally, the Mirror of Remote Viewing
can't offer a view indoors.
However, using magic,
I can create a sensory organ,
then by linking the two, I can...
No!
--What unpleasant creatures!
--Ugh...
--U-Um, I, er...
--Cocytus is just about to attack them!
--They should be given a punishment!
--Right! Absolutely right!
They really are rude, aren't they?!
Um... I, uh...
I'm so jealous...
Well, they are about to die.
I've seen in movies that in these situations,
the instinct to preserve the species kicks in,
or something. Mm-hmm.
--That is exactly correct!
--Yes, this much can be forgiven.
--Absolutely, absolutely!
--You are right, Lord Ains!
--U-Uh, that is, um...
--I wish Lord Ains and I could--
--All of you, be quiet!
Somehow, the wind
has gone out of my sails now...
Oh, crap! That was too soon for Aura and Mare!
What am I going to tell them
when they ask where babies come from?!
Turn to Albedo? Ugh, out of the question.
Demiurge? He can probably
explain it clinically. He's in the running.
Shalltear? Hmm, that doesn't actually
sound as bad as I would have expected.
Whatever the case,
it's a problem for a later date.
Ahem, Aura, since there has been
no activity at this stage,
the chances of coming into contact
with the one who used the world item
on Shalltear seem extremely low,
but remain vigilant to your surroundings.
Right!
If there is an Yggdrasil player
on the Lizard Men's side,
and they won't ally with us,
we must destroy them with our full force,
to keep any information from getting out.
Are you telling me that is Cocytus?
All right, Lord Ains is watching on, as well.
Show us your brilliance.
But before we start...
Ice Pillars!
As warriors who have the resolve to come here,
pardon the affront,
but I must make an announcement.
On this side of that gate is your destruction.
Know that if you advance
beyond there, death awaits you.
Hey, man, this guy's
surprisingly nice, isn't he?
You all stay there--no, return to the village.
Wha--?! No, let us fight with you!
It is not cowardly to withdraw! Nor is living!
Then--
But there are some of us
Lizard Men who cannot retreat!
You would not accept the rule of those of us
who stand as chiefs
if we did not fight, would you?!
But Chief, we're here to fight!
You youngsters go home.
This is a job for us older warriors.
Hmm.
Sorry to keep you, Cocytus!
Charge!
I hate to do this to warriors,
but I must first reduce your numbers.
Frost Aura!
Hmm, seems about right.
Those of us who are guardian class
have all acquired items and so forth
that grant us resistance to ranged weapons.
God Slaying Emperor Blade!
Martial Art, Iron Natural Weapon!
Iron Skin!
Hmm, yes indeed. Not a bad sword.
Tch!
You're in the way.
Over Magic! Mass Slight Cure Wounds!
You still have the will to fight?
Then I will return this to you.
That is getting annoying. Piercing Icicles!
Now then, there are two of you left?
Lord Ains said as much,
and sure enough, you two lasted until the end.
My brother, how hurt are you?
Badly. The pain is still throbbing.
Even so, I can swing my sword
a few more times.
You can? Then that will be enough.
The truth is, I am just about
out of magic power.
If I don't watch out,
I could collapse right here.
Is that right? Brother, you push yourself
too hard. But, all the same,
I will continue to swing my sword,
right up until the last moment!
A fine battle cry.
Outstanding, my brother! You're right!
Let's fight until the very end!
Now, let's not keep you waiting, Sir Cocytus!
It is no matter to me.
I am not so boorish as to
come between brothers saying farewell.
Prepare yourselves--no, I beg your pardon.
You had already prepared yourselves
before we even began.
Allow me to formally ask your names.
Shasuryu Shasha.
Zaryusu Shasha.
I shall remember them as the names of warriors.
Also, allow me to apologize in advance.
Normally, I would face you
with weapons in each hand,
but you are not mighty enough
for me to draw both.
That's a shame.
It sure is. Here goes!
Earth Bind!
My defense cannot be penetrated by one
whose magic level is inferior to mine!
Icy Burst!
If you wish to take me by surprise,
you should do it quietly!
Blood?
All of that, for this?
Magnificent.
I'm sorry, but I have a skill
that temporarily negates attacks
by weapons with weak magic power.
As long as it is activated,
your attacks are meaningless.
However...!
Cocytus, you fought admirably.
Thank you very much.
That being said, what you gave them
this time was the stick.
From here on,
what you must give them is the carrot.
It must not be a reign of terror.
I understand.
Very good. Listen to me, guardians.
The rule over the Lizard Men villages
is assigned to Cocytus.
If ever Cocytus requests
your support, assist him.
Lord Ains, what is to be
the disposition of those Lizard Men?
Those Lizard Men...?
Yes. The one called Zaryusu,
and the one called Shasuryu.
Ah, yes. Let's recover their bodies,
and use them as subjects
in the creation of undead
that do not rely on my skill.
I believe we can do better.
Hmm? What do you mean?
While they were weaklings,
I also saw in them the brilliance of warriors
who did not balk at someone
stronger than themselves.
I believe they have the potential
to become stronger than we assume.
Lord Ains, you have not conducted
any experiments in raising the dead.
What if you were to use them for that?
The brilliance of warriors, he calls it?
I see. They're too precious to pass up, then?
Is there anyone who can
represent the Lizard Men villages?
There was one white Lizard Man
with druidic powers,
who did not participate in the fighting.
That one? You don't say.
All right, how long will it take
to bring her here?
Forgive me, but assuming you would ask that,
I have called her to the next room already.
Ho?
Not at all. Well done, Cocytus.
Your judgment was on the mark.
All right, then, bring her in.
Yes, my lord.
Tell me your name.
Yes, Lord Ains Ooal Gown,
great and supreme king of death.
I am Crusch Lulu,
here on behalf of the Lizard Men.
Mm-hmm, thanks for coming.
Yes, Lord Gown. Please accept
the absolute allegiance of the Lizard Men.
Mm-hmm.
I have a special request for you.
If there is anything that I,
your loyal servant, can do, Lord Gown,
then please ask.
Not as my servant.
In return, I will return Zaryusu to life.
Is that possible...?
I am capable of manipulating
even life and death.
To me, death is nothing more
than a state of being.
Then, what do you desire of me,
your loyal slave?
Is it my body?
No, not exactly...
Ahem. Certainly not. It's simple.
I want you to keep a close watch to make sure
that there are no Lizard Men
who would betray me.
There are no such Lizard Men.
I am not so foolish as to actually believe that.
Right now, you have
a miracle hanging over you.
However, that miracle
will not necessarily last forever.
If you do not seize upon this moment,
it will all come to an end.
Crusch, what is the most important thing
to you? I want you to think about that.
I want you to covertly keep watch
on your fellow Lizard Men from the inside.
I will cast a special magic spell
on Zaryusu when I revive him.
If I determine that you have betrayed me,
the spell will immediately render him dead.
That will bring you grief.
However, it is a small price to pay
to have Zaryusu back, isn't it?
Except that there is no such spell.
Very well, Crusch Lulu, make your choice now.
Even if she declines, do nothing.
Well, what is your answer,
Crusch Lulu?
Zaryusu...
Zaryusu!
C-Crusch?!
Crusch, you were killed, too?
Huh?
Hmm, you have returned, but must be confused.
And it appears that some level loss
has occurred, as well.
I guess I can reason that
not much has changed after Yggdrasil.
What in the...?
Zaryusu Shasha,
first, allow me to congratulate you
on your resurrection.
R-Rethurrection...?
Y-You can bring the dead back to life?
Great One, I pledge my allegianth.
Very good. In the name of Ains Ooal Gown,
I give you my promise.
Prothperity for the Lithard Men.
Is that all? I can definitely
promise prosperity to all under my rule.
I offer my thankth.
Hmm, your speech is still faltering.
A little rest should remedy that.
Rest now. Then speak with Cocytus
about what is to follow.
Jutht a moment.
What about Thenberu and my brother?
Their bodies should still be around.
Can I athk you to pleathe
bring them back to life?
Hmm...
I don't see what that will gain me.
Then, why me? Thenberu and my brother
are thtrong. I'm thertain...
...they could be of uthe to you.
I'll consider it.
Keep their bodies safeguarded;
I'll take it under review.
Aura, let's go.
Right!
That hydra sure is cute, huh?
We thurvived--
or came back to life, at leatht...
It's all right. You can worry
about everything later, okay?
Right now, you have to rest,
and recover your strength.
Yeah...
Then that'th what I'll do...